<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Naked on Talking Heads Chords</title>
    <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Naked on Talking Heads Chords</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blind</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/blind/</guid>
      <description>Riff |557-557-5&amp;mdash;| |&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;| |&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;| |&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;| |&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;| |&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;|
riff + |:Dm (+6) :|
Signs Signs are lost Signs disappeared Turn invisible Got no sign Somebody got busted Got a face of stone And a ghostwritten biography Dogs start to run in, Hungry for some food Dogs start a-twitching And they&amp;rsquo;re looking at you It was light By five Torn all apart All in the name of democracy He&amp;rsquo;s hurt He&amp;rsquo;s dying Claimed he was a terrorist Claimed to avert a catastrophe Someone should&amp;rsquo;a told him That the buck stops here No one ever said That he was involved with thieves And they&amp;rsquo;re blind, blind blind, blind, blind, blind, blind blind, blind blind, blind, blind, blind, blind</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Jones</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/mr-jones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/mr-jones/</guid>
      <description>|:Em |C :| Mr. Jones Put a wiggle in your stride Loosen up I believe he&amp;rsquo;ll be alright Changing clothes Now he&amp;rsquo;s got ventilated slacks Bouncing off the walls Mr. Jones is back!
|:Em |D Em:| Bulge out And wind your waist Tight pants Got curly hair Drinking cold beer From metal cans Moonshine And Handi-Wipes!
|:C |G :| Mr. Jones is back in town it&amp;rsquo;s his lucky day Hold up your hands and shout Jones is on his way</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Totally Nude</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/totally-nude/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/totally-nude/</guid>
      <description>D Big and I&amp;rsquo;m bad And I want you to know I hand around Where the grass is greener Totally naked, baby Totally nude &amp;lsquo;Cause if I want to A Who&amp;rsquo;s gonna stop me? D A D I&amp;rsquo;m absolutely free D A D Living in the trees D A D The birdies and the bees A D &amp;lsquo;Cause I&amp;rsquo;m a nature boy
|:D |A :| Locked up inside You can&amp;rsquo;t tell me where it&amp;rsquo;s at Open up, open up, open the door Rocks and trees and physical culture Some days you hide I guess you wonder where you are Nature boy, nature man, take me along We got a life that&amp;rsquo;s undiscovered</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ruby Dear</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/ruby-dear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/ruby-dear/</guid>
      <description>|:C :| &amp;lsquo;Round and &amp;lsquo;round and we won&amp;rsquo;t let go And where we stop no one knows uh-huh uh-huh
Down and down in a spin we turn Looking like we&amp;rsquo;ll never learn uh-huh uh-huh
D Think about Bb what ev&amp;rsquo;ryone is saying D Bb Ruby dear, oh don&amp;rsquo;t you hear |:D | |Bb | :| Late at night when the radio is playing Ruby dear So looky here
|:C (Bb) C :| Oh this record&amp;rsquo;s broken It slips a beat And all those watermelons Have gone to seed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Nothing But) Flowers</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/nothing-but-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/nothing-but-flowers/</guid>
      <description>|:A |E |D :|
|:A |C#m |Bm |E :| Here we stand Like an Adam and an Eve Waterfalls The Garden of Eden Two fools in love So beautiful and strong The birds in the trees Are smiling upon them
|:G# |C#m :| From the age of the dinosaurs Cars have run on gasoline A C#m Where, where have they gone? Bm E Now, it&amp;rsquo;s nothing but flowers
|:A |E |D :| There was a factory Now there are mountains and rivers you got it, you got it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Democratic Circus</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/the-democratic-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/the-democratic-circus/</guid>
      <description>D Am(+7) D Am(+7) Found out this morning, there&amp;rsquo;s a circus coming to town D Am(+7) D Am(+7) They drive in Cadillacs, using walky talkies and the secret service E7 Asus4 E7 Asus4 Their big top, imitation of life E7 Asus4 E7 and all the flags and microphones E7 Asus4 they have to cover their eyes D Am(+7) D Am(+7) We play the sideshow and we like the tunnel of love D Am(+7) D Am(+7) And when we ride the ferris wheel, we&amp;rsquo;re little children again</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Facts Of Life</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/the-facts-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/the-facts-of-life/</guid>
      <description>&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;3&amp;mdash;-     &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;0&amp;ndash;   -0&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;   &amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;&amp;ndash;   &amp;mdash;0&amp;mdash;&amp;mdash;-    Em9 Mon key see and mon key do Ma king ba bies, ea ting food Smel ly things, pu bic hair Words of lo ve, in the air Sparks fly, shoo ting out Ma king sure that eve ry thing is wor king I can&amp;rsquo;t turn you down We are pro grammed hap py lit tle chil dren Mat ter o ver mind We can not re sis so I won&amp;rsquo;t fight it Love is a ma chine Love is a ma chine without a dri ver The facts of life The facts of life A masterpiece Biology Smokey water Air conditioned Boys &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; girls And automation Chromosomes Designer jeans Chimpanzees And human beings Machines of love Machines of love Strong in body, strong in mind A love machine with the facts of life The facts of life The facts of life So much sex &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; violence Must be a bad design We&amp;rsquo;re stupid to be fighting Every night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Daddy</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/big-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/big-daddy/</guid>
      <description>|:Gm :| C She had such tiny tears Bb Gm Just like a Barbie doll C She likes to shop at Sears Bb Gm And visit shopping malls C Now she&amp;rsquo;s a big mamma Tell poppa Bb Gm Cry, cry, cry, cry
Bb Gm Old Money Bb Gm Your old money doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter now Bb Gm Have mercy Bb Gm Mercy, mercy, daddy&amp;rsquo;s going fishing now Bb C He put the bait onto his line Bb C He&amp;rsquo;s winding out his reel Bb Gm Fish are swimming in the pond Bb C Gonna let &amp;lsquo;em sail away C |Bb |Gm :| Bb Gm He&amp;rsquo;s got his eye on you Bb C He knows just what she wants Bb Gm The fish is gonna bite Bb C She is his latest catch C &amp;lsquo;Cause he&amp;rsquo;s Big Daddy Oh, mammy C Gm Cry, cry, cry, cry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cool Water</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/cool-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/cool-water/</guid>
      <description>|:Bb |Dm :| |:Dm |G :|
|:D# |Dm :| Day by day &amp;hellip; Whistle while you work &amp;hellip; Our backs are breaking &amp;hellip; Up from hollow earth &amp;hellip; From end to end &amp;hellip; The noise begins &amp;hellip; In the human battle stations &amp;hellip; And the big one&amp;rsquo;s coming in
|:Dm |Gm :| Work, work, work, work &amp;hellip; Work till holes are filled &amp;hellip; Work, work, work, work &amp;hellip; Bags of bone and skin &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/bill/</guid>
      <description>|:Em |Em |Em A |A Em :|
Em Bill was a man Em A Who grew too big Em It didn&amp;rsquo;t matter what he did The girls would always run away A When everybody laughs at you Em It can be humiliating
Em Billy likes a Cute little girl They are lovers We can tell Gm Kisses on the mouth F Holding hands &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; all G#m G Look into their eyes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sax-and-violins</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/sax-and-violins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/naked/sax-and-violins/</guid>
      <description>|:D :| |:D C D:|
Falling falling Gonna drop like a stone I&amp;rsquo;m falling through the atmosphere On a warm afternoon If lovers discover That ev&amp;rsquo;ryone dies So don&amp;rsquo;t tell me, please hole me It&amp;rsquo;s a dangerous life
|:D :| Daddy dear Let&amp;rsquo;s get outta here I&amp;rsquo;m scared 10 o&amp;rsquo;clock Nighttime in New York It&amp;rsquo;s weird
Bm If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for trouble E That&amp;rsquo;s what you will find
|:D &amp;copy; D:| Mom &amp;amp; pop They will fuck you up For sure Love so deep Kills you in your sleep It&amp;rsquo;s true</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>