<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fear of Music on Talking Heads Chords</title>
    <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fear of Music on Talking Heads Chords</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Zimbra</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/i-zimbra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/i-zimbra/</guid>
      <description>|F | | | |
|:F | Fsus4 :|
GADJI BERI BIMBA CLANDRIDI LAULI LONNI CADORI GADJAM A BIM BERI GLASSALA GLANDRIDE |:Bb |C# :| E GLASSALA TUFFM I ZIMBRA
|:F | Fsus4 :| BIM BLASSA GALASSASA ZIMBRABIM |:Bb |C# :| BLASSA GLALLASSASA ZIMBRABIM |:F | Fsus4 :| A BIM BERI GLASSALA GRANDRID |:Bb |C# :| E GLASSALA TUFFM I ZIMBRA
|:Dm7 |Bb :| |C# | | | | |:Bb |C# :|</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/mind/</guid>
      <description>|:D :|
Time won&amp;rsquo;t change you Money won&amp;rsquo;t change you Bb F Bb F Bb F Bb F I haven&amp;rsquo;t got the faintest idea Gm Gm D# C D Am Everything seems to be up in the air at this time Am Bm G I need something you change your mind (4x)
|:D :| Drugs won&amp;rsquo;t change you Religion won&amp;rsquo;t change you Bb F Bb F Bb F Bb F I haven&amp;rsquo;t got the faintest idea Gm Gm D# C D Am Everything seems to be up in the air at this time Am Bm G I need something you change your mind (4x)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/paper/</guid>
      <description>|:G F:|8x
D C D C Hold the paper up to the light Am F (some rays pass right through) D C D C Expose yourself out there for a minute Am F (some rays pass right through)
|:Bb C Bb:| Take a little rest when the rays pass through Take a little time off when the rays pass through Go ahead and mis it up&amp;hellip; Go ahead and tie it up In a long distance telephone call</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cities</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/cities/</guid>
      <description>Intro: |:F#m |Em |Bm | :|
|:D :| Think of London, a small city It&amp;rsquo;s dark, dark in the daytime The people sleep, sleep in the daytime If they want to, if they want to
CHORUS C# I&amp;rsquo;m checking them out I&amp;rsquo;m checking them out D I got it figured out I got it figured out Dm D6 Dm D6 There&amp;rsquo;s good points and bad points F It all works out and though I&amp;rsquo;m a little freaked out I will F#m Find a city Em Bm Find myself a city to live in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life During Wartime</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/life-during-wartime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/life-during-wartime/</guid>
      <description>(What you&amp;rsquo;ll find below is probably a little different from the original. I only play accoustic and play this one with open chords. What I do is combining the baseline with the chords. The basic chord is Am which I vary with C all the time)
|:Am &amp;copy; |Am &amp;copy; |Am &amp;copy; |Am :|
Am C Am C Heard of a van that is loaded with weapons, Am C Am packed up and ready to go Am C Am C Heard of some gravesites, out by the highway, Am C Am a place that nobody knows Am C Am C The sound of gunfire, off in the distance, Am C Am I&amp;rsquo;m getting used to it now Am C Am C Lived in a brownstone, lived in the ghetto, Am C Am I&amp;rsquo;ve lived all over this town</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Air</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/air/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/air/</guid>
      <description>|:E7 |C7 :| Abm Air&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;Air (repeat) Fm Abm |Fm |D7 Hit me in the face E I run faster Abm Fm Abm Fm Faster faster faster faster faster into the air (I say to myself) C F What is happening to my skin? C F Where is that protection that I needed? Dm A Dm Air can hurt you too A Dm |Am E C D | Air can hurt you too C Dm Some people say not to worry about the air C Dm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memories Can&#39;t Wait</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/memories-cant-wait/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/memories-cant-wait/</guid>
      <description>|:C# | F# C# :|
Do you remember anyone here? No you don&amp;rsquo;t remember anything at all I&amp;rsquo;m sleeping, I&amp;rsquo;m flat on my back Never woke up, had no regrets
There&amp;rsquo;s a party in my mind&amp;hellip;And it never stops There&amp;rsquo;s a party up there all the time&amp;hellip;They&amp;rsquo;ll party till they drop B C B C Other people can go home&amp;hellip;Other people they can split B C B C I&amp;rsquo;ll be here all the time&amp;hellip;I can never quit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heaven</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/heaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/heaven/</guid>
      <description>D Em Everyone is trying to get to the bar. A G D The name of the bar, the bar is called Heaven. D Em The band in Heaven plays my favorite song. A G D They play it once again, they play it all night long.
Bm Am Heaven, heaven is a place C G A place where nothing, nothing ever happens. Bm Am Heaven, heaven is a place C G A place where nothing, nothing ever happens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animals</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/animals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/animals/</guid>
      <description>|:F#m7 :|
|:B Bbm :| I&amp;rsquo;m mad&amp;hellip;And that&amp;rsquo;s a fact I found out&amp;hellip;Animals don&amp;rsquo;t help Animal think&amp;hellip;They&amp;rsquo;re pretty smart Shit on the ground&amp;hellip;See in the dark.
|:Em7 Am7 :| They wander around like a crazy dog Make a mistake in the parking lot Always bumping into things Always let you down down down down.
|:F#m7 :| |:B Bbm :| Animals speak, they understand Trusting them is a big mistake Animals want to change my life I will ignore animals advise</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electric Guitar</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/electric-guitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/electric-guitar/</guid>
      <description>Am F#m E F F#m F Am F  Electric guitar is run over by a car on the highway Am Bb Gm C This is a crime against the state Bb F C This is the meaning of life. Am To tune this electric guitar F#m Em Fm F#m An electric guitar is brought in to a court of law Fm Am The judge and the jury (twelve members of the jury) F All listening to records Am Bb Gm C This is a crime against the state Bb F C This is the verdict they reach: Am Never listen to electric guitar F#m E Fm Electric guitar is copies, the copy sounds better F#m Fm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drugs (Electricity)</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/fear-of-music/drugs/</guid>
      <description>This song is pretty hard to do since there&amp;rsquo;s so much improvisation in it as well as several guitars dooing different things. So I only put down the basis here. The freaking out is up to you&amp;hellip;
G F-G And all I see is little dots G F-G Some are smeared and some are spots D C Bb G F-G Feels like a murder but that&amp;rsquo;s alright G F-G Somebody said there&amp;rsquo;s too much light G F-G Pull down the shade and it&amp;rsquo;s alright D C Bb G F-G It&amp;rsquo;ll be over in a minute or two.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>