<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speaking In Tongues on Talking Heads Chords</title>
    <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speaking In Tongues on Talking Heads Chords</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Burning Down The House</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/burning-down-the-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/burning-down-the-house/</guid>
      <description>G G F G  Ah____ Watch out you might get what you&amp;rsquo;re after G F G Cool babies strange but not a stranger F G I&amp;rsquo;m an ordinary guy A F Burning down the house
G G F Hold tight wait till the party&amp;rsquo;s over G G F G Hold tight We&amp;rsquo;re in for nasty weather F G There has got to be a way A F Burning down the house</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Flippy Floppy</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/making-flippy-floppy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/making-flippy-floppy/</guid>
      <description>Everybody: get in line
Fm7 Nothing can come between us Nothin gets you down Nothing strikes your fancy Nothing turns you on Somebody is waiting in the hallway Somebody is falling down the stairs Set someone free, break someone&amp;rsquo;s heart Stand up help us out
Ev&amp;rsquo;rything is divided Nothing is complete Ev&amp;rsquo;rything looks impressive Do not be deceived You don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait for more instructions No one makes a monkey out of me We lie on our backs, feet in the air Rest and relaxation, rocket to my brain F Snap into position G F Am G Bounce till you ache F Step out of line G F Am G And you end up in jail F Bring me a doctor G F Am G I have a hole in my head F But they are just people G F Am G And I&amp;rsquo;m not afraid</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Girlfriend Is Better</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/girlfriend-is-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/girlfriend-is-better/</guid>
      <description>This is again one of these songs that&amp;rsquo;s got one basic chord: Dm On the chorusses Dm7 is being played
Dm (10th fret) I &amp;hellip; Who took the money? Who took the money away? I &amp;hellip; It&amp;rsquo;s always showtime Here at the edge of the stage I, I, I, wake up and wonder What was the place, what was the name? We wanna wait, but here we go again&amp;hellip;
I &amp;hellip; takes over slowly But doesn&amp;rsquo;t last very long I &amp;hellip; no need to worry Evr&amp;rsquo;ything&amp;rsquo;s under control O - U - T But no hard feelings What do you know?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slippery People</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/slippery-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/slippery-people/</guid>
      <description>Am7 Whatabout the time? You were rollin&amp;rsquo; over Fall on your face You must be having fun Walk lightly! Think of a time. You&amp;rsquo;d best believe This think is real
Put away that gun This part is simple Try to recognize What is in you mind God help us! Help us loose our minds These slippery people help us understand
what&amp;rsquo;s the matter with him? He&amp;rsquo;s alright! I see his face The lord won&amp;rsquo;t mind Don&amp;rsquo;t play no games He&amp;rsquo;s alright Love from the bottom to the top Turn like a wheel He&amp;rsquo;s alright See for yourself The lord won&amp;rsquo;t mind We&amp;rsquo;re gonna move Right now Turn like a wheel inside a wheel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Get Wild / Wild Gravity</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/i-get-wild-wild-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/i-get-wild-wild-gravity/</guid>
      <description>|:Bm :| |Bm | C :| |:Bm | Bm+9 Bm:|
Fooled around enough with numbers Let&amp;rsquo;s not be ourselves today Is it just my imagination Is it just someone&amp;rsquo;s fave Pleasantly out of proportion It&amp;rsquo;s hard to hold on to the ground Now I didn&amp;rsquo;t come to run And this is everything And gravity lets you down
|:Bm :| I get wild, wizing up I just can&amp;rsquo;t let go I get wild when I get ready I can hardly talk Living lights Special lights Yellow turns blue I get wild It&amp;rsquo;s automatic I can hardly move</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swamp</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/swamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/swamp/</guid>
      <description>|:Am :| Am C Now lemme tell you a story Am C The devil he has a plan Am C A bag a&amp;rsquo; bones in his pocket Am D Am Got anything you want C Am C Am No dust and no rocks C Am The whole thing is over C Am C Am All these beauties in solid motion C Am D Am All those beauties, gonna swallow you up</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moon Rocks</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/moon-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/moon-rocks/</guid>
      <description>|:Bm7 | Bm7(+6) Bm7:| Flying saucers, levitation Yo! I could do that Get ready, for heavy duty Go one, give it a chance I saw your hair start to curl So get up, write it down You better wait for a while
|:Em :| So take your hands out of your pockets And get your face adjusted I heard it, somebody lied And I&amp;rsquo;m staring out the window Gonna let this thing continue In it&amp;rsquo;s natural time Roundheads squareheads Get settled in You can hear my belly rumble There&amp;rsquo;s a voice that starts to mumble Woo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pull Up The Roots</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/pull-up-the-roots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/pull-up-the-roots/</guid>
      <description>|:Bbm :| Hello again Yes indeed my friend I can tell Goin&amp;rsquo; get together again I could be right I could b ewrong I feel nice when I sing this song And I don&amp;rsquo;t mind Whatever happens is fine F# Baby likes to keep on playing &amp;hellip; Bbm What do I know, what do I know? F# Wilder than the place we live in &amp;hellip; Bbm
I&amp;rsquo;ll take you there, I&amp;rsquo;ll take you there F# I don&amp;rsquo;t mind some slight disorder &amp;hellip; Bbm Pull up the roots pull up the roots F# And I know ev&amp;rsquo;ry living creature .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Must Be The Place (Naive Melody)</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/this-must-be-the-place-naive-melody/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/speaking-in-tongues/this-must-be-the-place-naive-melody/</guid>
      <description>|:G |Am |Em |Am :| (repeat this the whole song through)
Home is where I want to be Pick me up and turn me around I feel numb, born with a weak heart I guess I must be having fun The less we say about it the better Make it up as we go along Feet on the ground, head in the sky It&amp;rsquo;s OK, I know nothing&amp;rsquo;s wrong.. nothing</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>