<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>True Stories on Talking Heads Chords</title>
    <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in True Stories on Talking Heads Chords</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Love For Sale</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/love-for-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/love-for-sale/</guid>
      <description>A C A I was born in a house with the television always on F Guess I grew up too fast G And I forgot my name A C We&amp;rsquo;re in cities at night and we got time on our hands. F So leave the driving to us. G And it&amp;rsquo;s the real thing.
 C  And you&amp;rsquo;re rolling D In the blender C With me. And I can love you D Like a color C TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puzzlin Evidence</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/puzzlin-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/puzzlin-evidence/</guid>
      <description>|:C :| |:Csus4 :| |:C |F D# :| You got the CBS&amp;hellip;! And the ABC&amp;hellip;! F You got Time and Newsweek! C F C Well, they&amp;rsquo;re the same to me!
C F Now don&amp;rsquo;t you wanna get right with me? C F D# (Puzzling Evidence) C F I hope you get ev&amp;rsquo;rything you need C F D# (Puzzling Evidence) C F D# Puzzling Evidence C F D# Puzzling Evidence C F D# Puzzling Evidence C F C F D# C F Done hardened in your heart D# C Hardened in your heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Now</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/hey-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/hey-now/</guid>
      <description>|:D | |A | :| D I wanna bicycle A I wanna popsicle D I wanna space face A Buy me a cherry face now
D Hey now! Hey now! A Hey now now! Hey now! Hey now! D Hey now now!
|:D | |A | :| I wanna video I wanna rock and roll Take me to the shopping mall Buy me a rubber ball now
Hey now! Hey now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papa Legba</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/papa-legba/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/papa-legba/</guid>
      <description>|:G (F) :| You&amp;rsquo;ll be, hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm, magnet for money You&amp;rsquo;ll be, mm-mm-mm-mm, magnet for love You&amp;rsquo;ll feel, hmm, light in your body Now I&amp;rsquo;m gonna say, gonna say these words:
F E Rompiendo la monotonia del tiempo F E Rompiendo la monotonia del tiempo
|:G (F)G:| It might hmm-mmm-mm-mm&amp;hellip;It might rain money It might hm-hi-hi-hi&amp;hellip;It might rain fire Now I&amp;rsquo;m gonna call, Gonna call on Legba. Get yourself a sign Get your love and desire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wild Wild Life</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/wild-wild-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/wild-wild-life/</guid>
      <description>|:E | B :|
E B I&amp;rsquo;m wearin&amp;rsquo; E B Fur pyjamas E B I ride a E B Hot Potata&amp;rsquo; C F G It&amp;rsquo;s tickling my fancy C F G Speak up, I can&amp;rsquo;t hear you
A Here on this mountaintop
D Woahoho E D A I got some wild, wild life I got some new to tell ya D Woahoho E D A About some wild, wild life Here comes the doctor in charge D Woahoho E D A She&amp;rsquo;s got some wild, wild life Ain&amp;rsquo;t that the way you like it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Head</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/radio-head/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/radio-head/</guid>
      <description>|:G |C D :|
G Baby your mind is a radio C D Got a reciever inside my head C D Baby I&amp;rsquo;m tuned to your wavelength C G Lemme tell you what it says:
C F G Transmitter! C G F G Oh! Picking up something good C F G Hey, radio head! C F D The sound&amp;hellip;of a brand-new world.
|:G |C D :| G So look at my fingers vibrate D From their tip down down to my toes C D Now I&amp;rsquo;m recieving your signal C G We&amp;rsquo;re gonna leave the land of noise</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Operator</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/dream-operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/dream-operator/</guid>
      <description>|:Am F |C :| C When you were little Em You dreamed you were big F You must have been something A real tiny kid C You wish you were me Em I wish I was you F Now don&amp;rsquo;t you wake up G The dream will come true
 C F G  Every dream has a name C G And names tell your story C F G This song is your dream C G You&amp;rsquo;re the dream operator |:Am F |C :| C It&amp;rsquo;s bigger than life Em You know it&amp;rsquo;s all me F My face is a book But it&amp;rsquo;s not what it seems C Three angels above Em The whole human race F They dream us to life G They dream me a face</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Like Us</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/people-like-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/people-like-us/</guid>
      <description>|G |D |C |D | |G |Bm |C |D |
G D C D In 1950 when I was born G Bm C D Papa couldn&amp;rsquo;t afford to buy us much F Bb F C He said be proud of what you are D A G There&amp;rsquo;s something special &amp;lsquo;bout people like us
Em G People like us C A (Who will answer the telephone) Em G People like us C D (Growing as big as a house) Em G People like us C D (Gonna make it because)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City of Dreams</title>
      <link>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/city-of-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://talking-heads.rosshudson.co.uk/talking-heads/true-stories/city-of-dreams/</guid>
      <description>|:G |C D :|
G C D Here where you are standing, the dinosaus did a dance G C D The indians told a story, now it has come to pass C G D The Indians had a legend, the Spaniards lived for gold C G D The white man came and killed them but they haven&amp;rsquo;t really gone
CHORUS G D C We live in the city of dreams G D C We drive on the highway of fire Am C Should we awake and find it gone D Remember this our favourite town</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>